https://www.saaf.org/site/privacy-policy/

Careers
Public Documents (990s, Annual Reports, etc.)
Care Services
New to SAAF?
Privacy Policy
This privacy policy sets out how the Southern Arizona AIDS Foundation (SAAF) uses and protects any information that you give us when you use this website.
SAAF is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.
SAAF may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 5/1/2012.
We may collect the following information:
name and job title
contact information including email address
demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests
other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers
We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:
Internal record keeping.
We may use the information to improve our products and services.
We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided. From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.
Security
We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How we use cookies
A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer’s hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.
We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.
Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.
You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.
Links to other websites
Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.
Controlling your personal information
We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen.
If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete or if you do not wish for us to share your information outside the agency, please write to us at 375 S. Euclid Ave., Tucson, AZ 85719 or email us at info@saaf.org as soon as possible. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
News and Events
SAAF Welcomes Dr. Ravi Grivois-Shah as its New Chief Executive Officer, September 30, 2020
The Southern Arizona AIDS Foundation, excitedly, welcomes Dr. Ravi Grivois-Shah as its new Chief Executive Officer. He is scheduled to begin his new role as CEO on Monday, September 28, 2020. Dr. Ravi comes to SAAF after serving as Medical Director of Alvernon Family Medicine and the UA Mobile Health Program, which provides free medical […]
Learn More
SAAF’s Next CEO, June 25, 2020
The SAAF Board of Directors is pleased to share with you that Dr. Ravi Grivois-Shah has been selected and hired to be the next Chief Executive Officer for SAAF.
Learn More
Save Lives By Supporting Virtual AIDSWALK Tucson 2020, October 2, 2020
By Rachel McMenamin, Grants Coordinator at the Southern Arizona AIDS Foundation As most things look different during this pandemic, so will the Southern Arizona AIDS Foundation’s annual AIDSWALK Tucson. For the safety of walkers, volunteers, clients, staff and our community, this year’s AIDSWALK has gone virtual. SAAF will host a week long AIDSWALK celebration from […]
Learn More
SAAF WINS BBB Torch Award in Nonprofit Ethics, May 14, 2019
We are honored to be the recipient of the BBB Serving Southern Arizona’s Torch Award for Nonprofit Ethics! As a nonprofit and more specifically as an AIDS service organization and an LGBTQ+ serving organization, we hold ourselves accountable to our stakeholders: our clients, our donors, the taxpayers, our staff and volunteers, our community partners, our funders, and […]
Learn More
Share the Love with SAAF’s Home-Bound Clients, December 26, 2018
Did you know that 92% of SAAF’s Food Program participants have extremely low and very low incomes and rely on our programs not just to avoid hunger, but to receive appropriate, nutrient-dense foods necessary to maintain their health and prevent HIV disease symptoms and medication side effects? Individuals living with HIV and their families face […]
Learn More
The mission of the Southern Arizona AIDS Foundation is to cultivate a healthy and stigma-free society through transformative action.
News and Events
About SAAF
In Response to COVID-19
SAAF’s History
Board of Directors
Staff
Careers
Public Documents (990s, Annual Reports, etc.)
HIV Prevention and Testing
Get Tested
Community Education
Thornhill Lopez Center on 4th
HIV/AIDS Facts
Prevention Programs
PrEP & PEP: Pre and Post Exposure Prophylaxis
Safer-Sex Practices
Hepatitis Information
Recreational Drug Information
Care Services
New to SAAF?
Case Management
Housing Services
Support Services
Anti-Violence Project
Food Programs
Pawsitive Friends Pet Food Bank
Support Groups
Travis Wright Memorial Buyers’ Club
Translate Website
Southern Arizona AIDS Foundation (SAAF)
375 South Euclid Avenue, Tucson, Arizona 85719
· PHONE: (520) 628-SAAF (7223) · TOLL FREE: (800)771-9054 · FAX: (520) 628-7222 · TTY:	(800) 367-8939
EMAIL: info@saaf.org
HOURS: 8:00am&emdash5:00pm Monday&emdashFriday
HIV/AIDS Content Notice: This site contains HIV prevention messages that may not be appropriate for all audiences. Since HIV infection is spread primarily through sexual practices or by sharing needles, prevention messages and programs may address these topics. If you are not seeking such information or may be offended by such materials, please exit this web site.
Website design and hosting by WhiteSpace DesignClick for Profile
